He actually found it
Is it yours
Yes
You saved me
I did help someone when I was a kid
But whether that person was you
needs to be verified
You don't want to just tell me it was you
I'm already your wife
I don't need to use a possible
favor to get you on my side
I'm meeting him tomorrow
He said he'll bring it
I'm going too
Of course since he has your old things
you definitely need to be there
Thank you
Mrs Fu doesn't need to keep thanking me
Don't let him fool you tomorrow
Do I look that gullible
No I'm just worried he'll turn my
things into his own story
He won't
Oh
Sister you're here too
Is it a bad time
Of course not
I'm just afraid you might misunderstand
Then make it clear
Don't let me misunderstand